eventfarm.com 2018-08-29

# Privacy Policy | Eventfarm

_This Privacy Policy was last reviewed and updated on May 11, 2018._

This website is owned and operated by Event Farm, Inc (“Event Farm", “Attend by Event Farm”, “Attend”, "we", "us" and/or "our") and has been created to provide information about our company and its enterprise event management, marketing, registration, and ticketing products and services. This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors of our website and users of our products (“you” and/or “your”), and to any information provided to us. By visiting our website or using our products (collectively, the “Service”), you are accepting the policies described herein.

This Privacy Policy sets forth our practices regarding collection and use of information about you. It also sets forth your options to access information about you that we collect, and your options to opt-out of our use and sharing of information. This Privacy Policy applies to transactions made, and information gathered, on our website and Service only and does not apply to any other website, even websites to which we provide links. You must contact that particular website operator or company to determine what its privacy practices are, which may be different than our practices. Also, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any contact that you have with us or our office outside of your usage of our Service via the internet.

Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. Each time you visit or use our Service or provide us with any information, you are hereby accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time. You expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your information as provided herein.

### Summary

  * **Types of Information We Collect:** We collect 2 types of information: "personally identifiable" information and non-"personally identifiable" information. In general, "personally identifiable" information means any type of information which could be utilized to personally identify or be readily associated with a specific user of this Service, including name, email, job title, company, phone number, and financial/payment information.

  * **How We Collect Information:** We collect information in 4 ways: (1) information that you knowingly and voluntarily input into our Service directly in response to particular prompts or fields; (2) information that is collected automatically when you use the Service; (3) information that is input into our Service from sources other than you, such as our Event Affiliates in connection with events listed on our Service; and (4) information about other people that users of the Service (including Event Affiliates) provide to us, including when you use the Service to send others (for example, attendees of prior events) invitations or messages through the Service. More information about how we collect information is set forth below.

  * **How We Use Personally Identifiable Information:** We use your personally identifiable information to perform transactions on the Service efficiently, deliver the services that you request directly from us or directly from one of our Event Affiliates through the Service, manage your account, provide you with customer service, enforce our Terms of Service, protect against or identify fraudulent transactions, contact you regarding the Service, your Account, and/or events for which you registered or purchased tickets on the Service (including event confirmations, changes and cancellations), and send information about events, offers and invitations to events, and other promotional materials to you from us and from selected third parties with whom we have a business relationship. More information about these uses is set forth below.

  * **How We Use Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** We use your other non-personally identifiable information to customize the Service to the interests of our users.

  * **How We Share Personally-Identifiable Information:** We do not sell personal information of users, no matter whether we obtain the information from you or from a third party. We may share your personally identifiable information with our agents, representatives, contractors, vendors, service providers, and credit card issuers/banks so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, order and ticket fulfillment, and promotional fulfillment. We may share your personally identifiable information with our Event Affiliates when you purchase a ticket or when you complete a registration form to any event listed on our Service. Your personally identifiable information may be given or transferred to a third party in connection with a transfer or sale of ownership or assets of our business, or in the event of a bankruptcy of our business. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to our affiliated legal entities and businesses. In addition, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to other parties when we, in our sole discretion, suspect or determine that our Service is being used for any unacceptable, inappropriate, or illegal purpose. We may also disclose this information where authorized by law or pursuant to any authorized law enforcement investigation, regardless of whether it was initiated by us or by another party. More information about how we share personal information is set forth below.

### What Information We Collect and How We Do It

Information can generally be collected in four ways: (1) information that you knowingly and voluntarily input into our Service directly in response to particular prompts or fields, including information input into affiliated services such as requests for demo or upgrade, survey responses, or customer service inquiries; (2) information that is collected automatically when you use the Service; (3) information that is input into our Service from sources other than you, such as our Event Affiliates in connection with events listed on our Service; and (4) information about other people that users of the Service (including Event Affiliates) provide to us, including when you use the Service to send others (for example, attendees of prior events) invitations or messages through the Service.

Some information can be "personally identifiable." We use the term "personally identifiable" information to mean any type of information which could be utilized to identify or be readily associated with you, the user of this Service. Examples of personally identifiable information include, but are not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, financial information, and e-mail address, or any combination thereof. In order to operate Our Service and provide you with information on events and services that may be of interest to you, We collect personally identifiable information (e.g. name, address, phone number, and e-mail address), financial information (e.g. passwords, credit/debit card numbers, bank, and other account numbers) and demographic information (e.g. zip code, hometown, gender, purchase history, and age) from you. Please note that, in some instances as described below, We treat financial information differently than we treat other types of personally identifiable information.

### Voluntary Release of Information

Whenever you are prompted by the Service to complete forms, provide payment information, and make choices, for example, and you choose to do so, you are voluntarily providing information to us. This information may or may not be personally identifiable, depending upon what you are asked to provide and how we use it. The transmission of an e-mail voluntarily initiated by you to us can also transmit personally identifiable information about you depending upon what information you choose to include in your email. You should not send personally identifiable information through our Service via unencrypted email, particularly information that you deem to be sensitive or confidential.

### Unsolicited Information

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to us through our Service or other means. All unsolicited information, including ideas for new products and product improvements or modifications, will be deemed to be non-confidential and we will be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such information to others without limitation or attribution.

### Automatic Collection of Information

The automatic collection of information refers to information collected from you that does not require you to provide information in response to particular fields or prompts. This can be done through the use of software or other automated processes that our Service uses.

For example, our Service, like many websites on the internet, use "cookies." A cookie is a small text file automatically placed on your computer's web browser that is used to recognize users who have previously visited the Service. In general, these cookies are either "persistent", meaning the files may reside on your computer for several months after you last accessed the Service (or until you delete or otherwise dispose of it), or on a temporary basis. Our Service also uses temporary cookies called "session cookies," which are stored for a single user session with the Service and are deleted as soon as your browser is shut down. We use cookies for purposes that include, but are not limited to, keeping track of your purchases and other activity on the Service, delivering content specific to your interests, saving your password, and if you choose, saving other personal and financial information so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Service. We do this to enhance your experience on our Service and to make it as easy to use as possible. Third-party advertisers on the Service may also place cookies on your browser. If you wish to disable these cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to do so. Please note, however, that if you choose to set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas of our Service.

Our Service uses “tracking pixels” to automatically collect information about you. Tracking pixels are a type of cookie that stores information about a website visitor and, in some cases, transfers this information to or from a third party. We use tracking pixels for the following purposes: (1) to obtain demographic and behavioral information about users of our Service, in order to improve our Service; and (2) for the purposes of marketing and remarketing--the practice of identifying past visitors to our Service in order to re-attract them to our Service through advertising.

  * We use Google Analytics’ third-party audience data, such as age, gender, and interests, to better understand our users.

  * We use third party companies, including Google AdWords, Facebook, and Adroll, that collect information about your online activities to provide advertising targeted to suit your interests and preferences. For example, you may see certain ads on other websites you visit because we contract with Google and other similar companies to target ads for our Service based on information collected by us or those third-party companies, including information collected through cookies and other automated means. These companies also use automated means to collect information about your interaction with our ads, such as whether or not you click on ads that are shown to you, which helps us keep track of and manage our marketing efforts.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to You using Google’s [Ad Settings Manager](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) tool, and can opt-out of transmitting data to Google Analytics using the [Google Analytics Opt-Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) tool. You can manage your opt-outs to other targeted advertising using the [Network Advertising Initiative's Opt Out Manager](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). Google services’ use of your data is outlined in the [Google Privacy Policy.](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US#infocollect)

Like most websites, each time you visit the Service, we automatically collect your "internet protocol" ("IP") address (and the website address that directed you to us, when applicable). An IP address is a unique series of numbers that identifies each computer connected to the internet. An IP address can be used to provide information such as the date and time of a user's visit, the availability of certain requested files, the popularity of various website functions, and the amount of information transmitted to each user from a site. Presently, we use your IP address to address the frequency of your visits to this Service and to determine the frequency with which certain pages and functions of the Service are accessed. This will allow us to improve the Service's functionality and to diagnose problems. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather demographic information.

You can inform the web services with which our Service integrates (such as social buttons, widgets, and other embedded features or content) that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits to be collected. Enabling "Do Not Track" in your web browser settings is an easy way to accomplish this. The "Do Not Track" browser setting is supported by recent versions of major browsers, including Firefox 5+, Internet Explorer 9+, Safari 5.1+, and Google Chrome. Please consult [www.donottrack.us](http://www.donottrack.us/) on how to enable this privacy setting on your browser. You can also change the way your browser handles cookies. Already existing cookies can be deleted. Please consult [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) on how to manage or delete cookies in your browser.

### Information Input into Our Service by Event Affiliates and Other Third Parties

We may also periodically obtain both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information about you from other business partners, contractors, and other third parties including Event Affiliates in connection with events listed on our Service, and add it to our account information or other information we have collected.

### Information about Others

We may also collect and store personally identifiable information about other people that you and other users of the Service (including Event Affiliates) provide to us. If you use the Service to send others (for example, attendees of prior events) invitations or messages through the Service, we may store your personally identifiable information, and the personally identifiable information of each such recipient. We use guests' contact information to allow them to respond to promotions and invitations to events.

### How We Use Your Personally Identifiable Information

We use your personally identifiable information for a variety of purposes, including, but not limited to, helping us to perform transactions on the Service efficiently, delivering the services that you request, managing your account, providing you with customer service, enforcing our Terms of Service, protecting against or identifying fraudulent transactions, contacting you regarding the Service, your account, and/or events for which you purchased tickets on the Service (including event confirmations, changes and cancellations), and sending information, offers, and other promotional materials to you from us and from selected third parties with whom we have a business and/or commercial relationship. You can use some aspects of our Service, including visiting certain portions of our website, without providing any personally identifying information. However, if you choose not to provide any personally identifying information, you may not be able to use certain portions of our Service. In some cases, access to your personally identifiable information may be necessary for our fulfillment of contractual obligations, such as access to your email address in order to provide you with login credentials to our Service.

### Retention of Personally Identifiable Information

Information submitted to us through our Service is retained indefinitely, in order to provide services as outlined in the “How We Use Your Personally Identifiable Information” section above, until and unless it is requested to be updated, corrected, or removed. Requests for corrections to or anonymization of the personally identifiable information we have about you can be submitted through [this form](https://support.eventfarm.com/hc/en-us/requests/new) or via email to [legal@eventfarm.com](mailto:legal@eventfarm.com) and will be honored as outlined and required by applicable law.

### Opting Out of Offers

From time to time, we send offers that we believe would be of interest and value to you, such as discounts, exclusive deals, information about events, offers and invitations to events, and other promotional materials from us and from selected third parties with whom we have a business relationship. Effective May 25, 2018, new users of our Service will be required to opt-in to these communications at the time when you provide your contact information to us. For users of our Service prior to that date, or any users wishing to no longer receive these communications, we provide you with the option of declining to receive these types of offers from us by "opting-out" or "unsubscribing" from future offers. By opting-out or unsubscribing, We give you the choice to not receive these types of communications, although we will still contact you regarding any specific events to which you have purchased tickets. You will be given the option to opt-out or unsubscribe after you receive your first offer from us. We will provide a link that you can use to opt-out or unsubscribe of receiving subsequent marketing emails sent by us. Please note, however, that opting-out of receipt of email communications from us and/or third parties, but not Event Affiliates (as defined below) (or by otherwise changing or deleting your account information), will only change the information in our database for future transactions and communications from us and/or third parties. These changes will not affect: (1) information already collected as part of a particular ticket purchase in our database which may be shared with our Event Affiliates regardless of your email preferences; and (2) information that we may have already forwarded to Event Affiliates, credit card companies, or any other third parties, as provided above. In this instance, you would have to contact each of those entities individually in order to make any changes to their use of your personally identifiable information. If you opt-out and you still receive these offers directly from us, please contact us at [legal@eventfarm.com](mailto:legal@eventfarm.com) as soon as possible so that we can add your name to our opt-out list.

Unless you opt-out, we will use and disclose all information submitted by you for such third-party offers in the same manner in which we use and disclose all other information submitted by you for offers we sponsor. We may select third parties with whom we will share your personally identifiable information so that they can communicate directly with you about their products and services. We have no control over third parties and cannot guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with other parties, as they may have different privacy practices as to how your information will be handled.

### How We Share Your Personally Identifiable Information

We do not sell personal information of users, no matter whether we obtain the information from you or from a third party. In order to process transactions and payments on the Service, we will share your personally identifiable information with our agents, representatives, contractors, vendors, service providers, and credit card issuers/banks so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, order and ticket fulfillment, and promotional fulfillment. We have no control over these parties and cannot guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with other parties, as they may have different privacy practices as to how your information will be handled.

When you purchase a ticket or submit a registration form to any event listed on our Service, we will share your personally identifiable information with the venues, promoters, producers, organizers, managers, presenters, artists, teams, organizations, business partners, authorized service providers and other third-parties associated with that particular event ("Event Affiliates"). We cannot offer you a separate opportunity to opt-out, or not to consent, to our sharing of your personally identifiable information with these parties, as explained below. Event Affiliates may use your information in accordance with their own privacy policies, and may consequently use your personally identifiable information to contact you and may share your personally identifiable information with others. You must contact those Event Affiliates directly to instruct them regarding your preferences for their use of your personally identifiable information.

Your personally identifiable information may be given or transferred to a third party in connection with a transfer or sale of ownership or assets of our business, or in the event of a bankruptcy of our business. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to our affiliated legal entities and businesses. However, all of the affiliated legal entities and businesses that receive your personally identifiable information from us will comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy with respect to their use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information. In addition, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to other parties when we, in our sole discretion, suspect or determine that our Service is being used for any unacceptable, inappropriate, or illegal purpose. We may also disclose this information where authorized by law or pursuant to any authorized law enforcement investigation, regardless of whether it was initiated by us or by another party.

### How We Use Financial Information

Personally identifiable information includes financial information. Therefore, we use the term "financial information" as a sub-category of personally identifiable information relating to credit card, billing, and payment information that you provide to us when you transact business on our Service. We use your financial information to bill you for products and services and to enable you to participate in discount, rebate, and similar programs in which you choose to participate. By making a purchase or engaging in any other kind of activity that uses financial information on our Service, you hereby consent and allow us to provide your financial information to our Event Affiliates, service providers, credit card companies, banking institutions, processing centers, and/or to such other third parties as we determine to be necessary to handle and process your transactions. Except as provided below, we do not make your financial information available to third parties unrelated to a particular event or transaction without your consent.

In addition, as stated earlier with regard to personally identifiable information generally, depending upon the circumstances of our registration or ticketing service arrangements with particular venues and event promoters, we may share your financial information with applicable Event Affiliates for the primary purpose of dispute resolution and customer service at the venue on, before or after the date of the event. This sharing of your financial information may be necessary in order for you to gain admittance to the event and for identification verification purposes or to otherwise resolve any problems that occur while at the event.

As noted above with personally identifiable information, financial information may be given or transferred to a third party in connection with a transfer or sale of ownership or assets of Event Farm, or in the event of a bankruptcy of Event Farm. We may also disclose your financial information to our subsidiary and parent companies and businesses, and other affiliated legal entities and businesses. However, all of the affiliated legal entities and businesses that receive your financial information from us will comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy with respect to their use and disclosure of your financial information. In addition, we will disclose your financial information to other parties when we, in our sole discretion, suspect or determine that our Service is being used for any unacceptable, inappropriate, or illegal purpose. We may also disclose this information where authorized by law or pursuant to any authorized law enforcement investigation, regardless of whether it was initiated by us or by another party.

### How We Use Other Information

We use your other non-personally identifiable information, such as general demographic information, to customize the Service to the interests of our users. We may share this information with our Event Affiliates. We may also share anonymous, aggregated demographic information with advisors, advertisers, investors and other third parties for general business analysis purposes and so that advisors can customize their advertisements, promotions, and communications to the appropriate audience. There may also be certain instances when we provide third parties with your personally identifiable and specific demographic information on a non-anonymous basis. We will not, however, knowingly and intentionally provide these parties with your financial information.

### Your Postings

We may provide areas on our Service where you can post information about yourself, communicate with others, post reviews or upload content. Whenever you disclose personal information publicly (such as on publicly viewable web pages), that information becomes public and can be collected and used by others. We can't control who reads your posting or what others may do with information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to use your discretion with respect to posting personal information. Also, such postings are governed by our Terms of Service, so be sure to review them before posting.

### Personally Identifiable Information of Minor Children

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personally identifiable information through our Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide personally identifiable information through our Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifiable information to Event Farm through our Service, please contact us at [legal@eventfarm.com](mailto:legal@eventfarm.com), and we will endeavor to remove that information from our databases.

### Visiting Our Service from outside the United States

This Privacy Policy covers the collection of information on the Service from United States residents. If you are visiting the Service from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. United States data protection and other laws may not be as comprehensive as those in your country.

### Rights of Citizens of the European Union ("E.U.")

The General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) outlines specific protections for E.U. citizens with regards to the processing, protection, and privacy of your personal data. As of May 25, 2018, Event Farm is fully compliant with the requirements of the GDPR for all applicable persons. The following is a summarized list of rights of E.U. citizens under GDPR and how we respect them under our Privacy Policy. This list is not intended to be a full explanation of citizens’ rights under the GDPR, but is provided for your guidance in understanding your rights under our Privacy Policy. Where interpretation of your rights under the GDPR differs from interpretation of this section of our Privacy Policy, the rights as outlined in the GDPR supercede those as outlined in this section.

  * **The right to access** \- You have the right to confirmation as to whether or not and where we process your personally identifiable information, as well as access to the personally identifiable information we have about you. Providing the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of the personally identifiable information we have about you. The first copy will be provided free of charge, but additional copies may be subject to a reasonable fee.

  * **The right to rectification** \- You have the right to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, where relevant to the ability for us to process your data, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.

  * **The right to erasure** \- You have the right, except where restrictions apply, to request the removal of your personally identifiable information from our system without undue delay. This right applies if your personally identifiable information is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, if you withdraw your consent for data processing, if you object to the processing of your data, if your data is being processed unlawfully, if there is a legal requirement for your data to be erased, or if you were a child at the time of data collection. This right does not apply where your data is necessary for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information, for complying with a legal obligation, or for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.

  * **The right to restrict processing** \- You have the right, under some circumstances, to restrict the processing of your personally identifiable information. These circumstances under which you can exercise this right are if you contest the accuracy of your personally identifiable information, if processing is unlawful but you choose not to exercise your right to erasure, if your data is no longer necessary to us for processing but you request it to be retained for the purposes of the establishment, exercise, or defense of a legal claim, and if you wish to exercise your right to object to processing but verification of your objection is still pending. After exercising your right to restrict data processing, we may continue to store your data, but will only process it with your consent, as legally required, where necessary for the protection of another person’s rights, or for reasons of important public interest.

  * **The right to object to processing** \- You have the right to object to our processing of your personally identifiable information, except where we have demonstrable legitimate grounds to process your data which override your interests, rights, and freedoms, or where processing your data is necessary for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims. You have the right to object to our processing of your data for direct marketing purposes; if you exercise this right, we will cease to use your data for this purpose. You have the right to object to our processing of your data for research or statistical purposes, unless this processing is necessary for performance of a task being carried out for reasons of public interest.

  * **The right to data portability** \- When the processing of your data is carried out by automated means and on the legal basis of consent or as a necessity to perform contractually obligated services, you have the right to receive your data in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format, except where it would adversely affect the rights of others.

  * **The right to complain to a supervisory authority** \- If you believe that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have the right to complain to a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your workplace, or the place of the alleged infringement.

  * **The right to withdraw consent** \- Where the legal basis of our processing of your data is consent, you have the right to withdraw consent at any time. This withdrawal of consent is not retroactive, and does not affect the lawfulness of previously-processed data.

Requests regarding any of the above rights can be submitted [here](https://support.eventfarm.com/hc/en-us/requests/new).

### Our Security Precautions

We attempt to protect your personally identifiable information by utilizing reasonable security measures to prevent loss, misuse, alteration, unintentional destruction or unauthorized access. We use secure server software (SSL) for your Service transactions. We encrypt all of your personally identifiable information as it travels over the Internet and we store your financial information on our servers in encrypted form. However, no system can be completely secure. Although we take significant steps to secure your information, there is always a chance that your information will not always remain secure, and you should always take great care in handling and disclosing your personally identifiable information. If you learn that our security measures have been compromised or have other concerns, please inform us immediately at [legal@eventfarm.com](mailto:legal@eventfarm.com).

### Access to Your Personally Identifiable and Other Information

When you register to create an account with the Service or complete a purchase transaction on the Service, we will either give you the opportunity to set certain email preferences when you register or make your purchase, or we will automatically set certain email preferences for you. When you receive a confirmation email from us confirming your registration or purchase, you will be provided with a link to change these preferences or your registration information. As noted earlier, however, changing your preferences will only affect future communications directly from us and not from Event Affiliates or other third parties who may have already received your information.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. If we make a material change to our privacy practices, we will provide notice on our website or by other means as appropriate.

If we are required by law to obtain your consent to any material changes before they come into effect, then we will do so in accordance with law.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or the practices of the Service, you can contact us at [legal@eventfarm.com](mailto:legal@eventfarm.com), by phone at (888) 444-8162, or by mail through our Corporate Office located at Event Farm, Inc., 2448 Main Street, Santa Monica, CA 90405.

### Data Protection Officer

Our Data Controller and Data Protection Officer is Todd Cornett, CTO. Inquiries can be directed to him ℅ Event Farm, Inc. at [legal@eventfarm.com](mailto:legal@eventfarm.com), by phone at (888) 444-8162, or by mail through our Corporate Office located at Event Farm, Inc., 2448 Main Street, Santa Monica, CA 90405.
